<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>UK &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<atom:link href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/tag/uk/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/r4s.png</url>
	<title>UK &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cross the Atlantic Ocean in a balloon</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On this day in history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=45</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[British billionaire Richard Branson and Swedish aviator Per Lindstrand set a unique record. On this day in 1987, they crossed the Atlantic Ocean in a hot-air balloon. No one before them could achieve this feat. Through this, Richard and Lindstrand set a world record. Departing from Maine, USA, they landed in Limavady, Northern Ireland. Passed ... <a title="Cross the Atlantic Ocean in a balloon" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/" aria-label="More on Cross the Atlantic Ocean in a balloon">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>British billionaire Richard Branson and Swedish aviator Per Lindstrand set a unique record. On this day in 1987, they crossed the Atlantic Ocean in a hot-air balloon. No one before them could achieve this feat. Through this, Richard and Lindstrand set a world record. Departing from Maine, USA, they landed in Limavady, Northern Ireland. Passed 4 thousand 947 kilometers or about 3 thousand 74 miles.</p>



<p>The time was July 3, 1938. Railway steam engine Mallard sets a new record near Grantham, UK. The top speed of the engine that day was 203 kilometers per hour or about 126 miles per hour. So far no steam railway engine has broken this record.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">First automobile on the way</h2>



<p>On July 3, 1886, the world&#8217;s first automobile was driven on German roads. The three-wheeled motor wagon was driven by engineer Karl Benz.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Longest ring chain</h2>



<p>3 July 2004. In Cleveland, USA, a group of magicians made a chain by connecting steel rings one by one. The leader of this group was magician Monty Witt. There were 129 other magicians in the team. The chain they made by connecting 534 steel rings in a row set a world record.</p>



<p>Tom Cruise is a very popular Hollywood actor. This American actor has played lead roles in more than 40 films. He has hit films like Ton Gun, Mission Impossible series. Today is Tom Cruise&#8217;s birthday. He was born on July 3, 1962.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
