<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>journalist &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<atom:link href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/tag/journalist/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:23:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/r4s.png</url>
	<title>journalist &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>In Iran, a female journalist was sentenced to 5 years in prison</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[journalist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A prominent Iranian rights activist and journalist, Golrokh Irai, has been sentenced to five years in prison by an appeals court in the country. His supporters gave this information on Sunday. Irai was initially sentenced to seven years in prison last April for taking part in &#8216;illegal&#8217; rallies and violating national security. He refused to ... <a title="In Iran, a female journalist was sentenced to 5 years in prison" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/" aria-label="More on In Iran, a female journalist was sentenced to 5 years in prison">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A prominent Iranian rights activist and journalist, Golrokh Irai, has been sentenced to five years in prison by an appeals court in the country. His supporters gave this information on Sunday.</p>



<p>Irai was initially sentenced to seven years in prison last April for taking part in &#8216;illegal&#8217; rallies and violating national security. He refused to participate in the hearing of the appeal against this verdict. According to the rights groups, Irai thinks that this court is not justified.</p>



<p>Irai was arrested by police at his home last September at the start of nationwide protests against the death of Kurdish teenager Masa Amini in police custody in Iran. Masa was arrested by the country&#8217;s policy police for violating the hijab policy. Masa died in police custody on September 16.</p>



<p>&#8220;Golrokh Irai, who has been in Evin prison for 280 days, has been sentenced to 5 years in prison by a Tehran court,&#8221; a Twitter account in Irai&#8217;s name said. This Twitter account is run by his supporters.</p>



<p>Irai is well known for campaigning against issues including stoning and prison conditions. Her husband, Arash Sadeghi, another rights activist, was also arrested during protests against the &#8216;killing&#8217; of Massa Amini, but is now free.</p>



<p>Several rights activists have been arrested during Iran&#8217;s crackdown on protest movements. However, they were released after the protests subsided in the last few months.</p>



<p>However, several prominent women&#8217;s rights activists are still in jail. Among them are Nargis Mohammadi, labor rights activist Sepideh Gholian and environmental campaigners Nilofar Bayani and Sepideh Kashani. Apart from Irai, two other female journalists, Nilufar Hamedi and Ilahe Mohammadi, have been imprisoned since September. They are on trial in Tehran on charges of violating national security.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
