<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>itannica &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<atom:link href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/author/itannica/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/r4s.png</url>
	<title>itannica &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cross the Atlantic Ocean in a balloon</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[On this day in history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=45</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[British billionaire Richard Branson and Swedish aviator Per Lindstrand set a unique record. On this day in 1987, they crossed the Atlantic Ocean in a hot-air balloon. No one before them could achieve this feat. Through this, Richard and Lindstrand set a world record. Departing from Maine, USA, they landed in Limavady, Northern Ireland. Passed ... <a title="Cross the Atlantic Ocean in a balloon" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/" aria-label="More on Cross the Atlantic Ocean in a balloon">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>British billionaire Richard Branson and Swedish aviator Per Lindstrand set a unique record. On this day in 1987, they crossed the Atlantic Ocean in a hot-air balloon. No one before them could achieve this feat. Through this, Richard and Lindstrand set a world record. Departing from Maine, USA, they landed in Limavady, Northern Ireland. Passed 4 thousand 947 kilometers or about 3 thousand 74 miles.</p>



<p>The time was July 3, 1938. Railway steam engine Mallard sets a new record near Grantham, UK. The top speed of the engine that day was 203 kilometers per hour or about 126 miles per hour. So far no steam railway engine has broken this record.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">First automobile on the way</h2>



<p>On July 3, 1886, the world&#8217;s first automobile was driven on German roads. The three-wheeled motor wagon was driven by engineer Karl Benz.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Longest ring chain</h2>



<p>3 July 2004. In Cleveland, USA, a group of magicians made a chain by connecting steel rings one by one. The leader of this group was magician Monty Witt. There were 129 other magicians in the team. The chain they made by connecting 534 steel rings in a row set a world record.</p>



<p>Tom Cruise is a very popular Hollywood actor. This American actor has played lead roles in more than 40 films. He has hit films like Ton Gun, Mission Impossible series. Today is Tom Cruise&#8217;s birthday. He was born on July 3, 1962.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/cross-the-atlantic-ocean-in-a-balloon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter specified how many tweets can be read per day</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/twitter-specified-how-many-tweets-can-be-read-per-day/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/twitter-specified-how-many-tweets-can-be-read-per-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Social networking site Twitter has set a temporary limit on the number of tweets users can read in a day. Elon Musk, the owner of this social media, announced this last Sunday. Elon Musk announced on Twitter that a maximum of 600 posts per day can be read from accounts that are not verified. 300 ... <a title="Twitter specified how many tweets can be read per day" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/twitter-specified-how-many-tweets-can-be-read-per-day/" aria-label="More on Twitter specified how many tweets can be read per day">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Social networking site Twitter has set a temporary limit on the number of tweets users can read in a day. Elon Musk, the owner of this social media, announced this last Sunday.</p>



<p>Elon Musk announced on Twitter that a maximum of 600 posts per day can be read from accounts that are not verified. 300 posts can be read from new accounts that are not verified.</p>



<p>But in case of verified account, the number of daily post reading will be 6 thousand. Elon Musk says data theft has &#8216;reached extremes&#8217;. To combat this, user posts are temporarily limited.</p>



<p>Last Friday, many users were asked to log in to view tweets. Musk said the conditions were imposed on users as an immediate emergency measure.</p>



<p>Arguing in favor of limiting users&#8217; tweets, Elon Musk said that Twitter&#8217;s &#8220;stacks&#8221; of data are reducing the quality of service for ordinary users.</p>



<p>Elon Musk bought Twitter for 4 thousand 4 billion US dollars last year after many struggles. After becoming the owner, he announced layoffs. In one blow, the employees of the company were reduced from 8 thousand to 1500.</p>



<p>He had to face a lot of criticism for this. Elon Musk then canceled the opportunity to become a verified user (blue ticked account) on Twitter for free. Now in exchange for money user account has blue tick.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/twitter-specified-how-many-tweets-can-be-read-per-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Messi-Ronaldo on Garnacho&#8217;s birthday</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cristiano ronaldo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[English Premier League]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manchester United]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Messi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portugal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alejandro Garnacho would be at the top of any short list of future stars or the best emerging footballers of all time. The Argentine winger, who emulates Cristiano Ronaldo, finished last season in fine form for Manchester United . A few days ago, Argentina also made its debut in the national team. I mean, Garnacho ... <a title="A Messi-Ronaldo on Garnacho&#8217;s birthday" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/" aria-label="More on A Messi-Ronaldo on Garnacho&#8217;s birthday">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Alejandro Garnacho would be at the top of any short list of future stars or the best emerging footballers of all time. The Argentine winger, who emulates Cristiano Ronaldo, finished last season in fine form for Manchester United . A few days ago, Argentina also made its debut in the national team.</p>



<p>I mean, Garnacho had Ronaldo as a teammate at United, then Lionel Messi at the Argentina national team. Playing alongside two of the best footballers of this century is naturally a dream come true for Garnacho.</p>



<p>Not only on the field, but also outside the field, Garnacho is enjoying his time. Parshui passed through adolescence and entered adulthood. Cut the 19th birthday cake. Messi-Ronaldo also came to wish him a happy evening on a special day!</p>



<p>Wondering? This Messi-Ronaldo is not real. In fact, Messi-Ronaldo was disguised by two thin men, who are called &#8216;Dwarf Messi-Ronaldo&#8217;. &#8216;Dwarf Messi&#8217; Argentina and &#8216;Dwarf Ronaldo&#8217; came in Portugal jerseys. However, some in attendance claimed that the jersey &#8216;Mini Messi&#8217; was wearing belonged to Garnacho&#8217;s club and national teammate Lisandro Martinez.</p>



<p>It was Messi-Ronaldo who held the birthday cake modeled after the national flag of Argentina and the logo of the Football Association (AFA). Garnacho also took pictures with them. Thanks to social media, that picture is now at the center of discussion.</p>



<p>Garnacho&#8217;s birthday cake had &#8217;19&#8217; written on top of a football design. Which naturally meant his 19th birthday. But in the middle of the cake was written &#8216;7&#8217;. And by seeing this number, the curiosity of the fans has disappeared. A few days ago, the European media reported that Garnacho will get Cristiano Ronaldo&#8217;s iconic number 7 jersey next season after gaining the trust of United coach Eric Ten Haag . After seeing the number &#8216;7&#8217; on the birthday cake, fans made two-two-four.</p>



<p>In 2021, Ronaldo returned to United after an era in a dramatic change of team. Edinson Cavani willingly took the number 21 jersey and gave Ronaldo back his well-known &#8216;number seven&#8217;. But CRSeven&#8217;s second chapter at the English Premier League&#8217;s most successful club has not been pleasant. The Portuguese forward became a member of the team after Eric ten Haag became the coach of the Red Devils. In an interview with journalist Piers Morgan before the World Cup in Qatar last year, he made explosive comments about the club and the coach. After that, United canceled the contract with Ronaldo .</p>



<p>The number 7 jersey has not been handed to anyone since Ronaldo left Old Trafford midway through the 2022–23 season. Because, according to Premier League rules, no player can change jersey number during the season. Now that the season is over, there&#8217;s no stopping him from wearing the iconic jersey number.</p>



<p>Garnacho, who has been wearing the number 49 jersey for United for so long, is getting his ideal Ronaldo jersey next season. The young winger posted a picture wearing the number 7 on his Instagram story. Now it&#8217;s time to match yourself like Ronaldo.</p>



<p>Garnacho scored 5 goals and 4 assists in 34 games for United in all competitions last season. These statistics may seem, what else! But in 19 of these 34 matches, he was brought down as a substitute. The opportunity to play full 90 minutes was given in only 2 matches. He was out of the field for 7 matches due to an injury in the middle. The way Garnacho is making the most of this limited opportunity was enough for Ronaldo to get the number 7 jersey. As United&#8217;s new &#8216;number seven&#8217;, Garnacho will surely get more time on the field next season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Iran, a female journalist was sentenced to 5 years in prison</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[journalist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A prominent Iranian rights activist and journalist, Golrokh Irai, has been sentenced to five years in prison by an appeals court in the country. His supporters gave this information on Sunday. Irai was initially sentenced to seven years in prison last April for taking part in &#8216;illegal&#8217; rallies and violating national security. He refused to ... <a title="In Iran, a female journalist was sentenced to 5 years in prison" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/" aria-label="More on In Iran, a female journalist was sentenced to 5 years in prison">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A prominent Iranian rights activist and journalist, Golrokh Irai, has been sentenced to five years in prison by an appeals court in the country. His supporters gave this information on Sunday.</p>



<p>Irai was initially sentenced to seven years in prison last April for taking part in &#8216;illegal&#8217; rallies and violating national security. He refused to participate in the hearing of the appeal against this verdict. According to the rights groups, Irai thinks that this court is not justified.</p>



<p>Irai was arrested by police at his home last September at the start of nationwide protests against the death of Kurdish teenager Masa Amini in police custody in Iran. Masa was arrested by the country&#8217;s policy police for violating the hijab policy. Masa died in police custody on September 16.</p>



<p>&#8220;Golrokh Irai, who has been in Evin prison for 280 days, has been sentenced to 5 years in prison by a Tehran court,&#8221; a Twitter account in Irai&#8217;s name said. This Twitter account is run by his supporters.</p>



<p>Irai is well known for campaigning against issues including stoning and prison conditions. Her husband, Arash Sadeghi, another rights activist, was also arrested during protests against the &#8216;killing&#8217; of Massa Amini, but is now free.</p>



<p>Several rights activists have been arrested during Iran&#8217;s crackdown on protest movements. However, they were released after the protests subsided in the last few months.</p>



<p>However, several prominent women&#8217;s rights activists are still in jail. Among them are Nargis Mohammadi, labor rights activist Sepideh Gholian and environmental campaigners Nilofar Bayani and Sepideh Kashani. Apart from Irai, two other female journalists, Nilufar Hamedi and Ilahe Mohammadi, have been imprisoned since September. They are on trial in Tehran on charges of violating national security.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/in-iran-a-female-journalist-was-sentenced-to-5-years-in-prison/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
