<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Messi &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<atom:link href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/tag/messi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:33:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/r4s.png</url>
	<title>Messi &#8211; R4s31 Cam Britannica</title>
	<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Messi-Ronaldo on Garnacho&#8217;s birthday</title>
		<link>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/</link>
					<comments>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[itannica]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cristiano ronaldo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[English Premier League]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manchester United]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Messi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portugal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alejandro Garnacho would be at the top of any short list of future stars or the best emerging footballers of all time. The Argentine winger, who emulates Cristiano Ronaldo, finished last season in fine form for Manchester United . A few days ago, Argentina also made its debut in the national team. I mean, Garnacho ... <a title="A Messi-Ronaldo on Garnacho&#8217;s birthday" class="read-more" href="https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/" aria-label="More on A Messi-Ronaldo on Garnacho&#8217;s birthday">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Alejandro Garnacho would be at the top of any short list of future stars or the best emerging footballers of all time. The Argentine winger, who emulates Cristiano Ronaldo, finished last season in fine form for Manchester United . A few days ago, Argentina also made its debut in the national team.</p>



<p>I mean, Garnacho had Ronaldo as a teammate at United, then Lionel Messi at the Argentina national team. Playing alongside two of the best footballers of this century is naturally a dream come true for Garnacho.</p>



<p>Not only on the field, but also outside the field, Garnacho is enjoying his time. Parshui passed through adolescence and entered adulthood. Cut the 19th birthday cake. Messi-Ronaldo also came to wish him a happy evening on a special day!</p>



<p>Wondering? This Messi-Ronaldo is not real. In fact, Messi-Ronaldo was disguised by two thin men, who are called &#8216;Dwarf Messi-Ronaldo&#8217;. &#8216;Dwarf Messi&#8217; Argentina and &#8216;Dwarf Ronaldo&#8217; came in Portugal jerseys. However, some in attendance claimed that the jersey &#8216;Mini Messi&#8217; was wearing belonged to Garnacho&#8217;s club and national teammate Lisandro Martinez.</p>



<p>It was Messi-Ronaldo who held the birthday cake modeled after the national flag of Argentina and the logo of the Football Association (AFA). Garnacho also took pictures with them. Thanks to social media, that picture is now at the center of discussion.</p>



<p>Garnacho&#8217;s birthday cake had &#8217;19&#8217; written on top of a football design. Which naturally meant his 19th birthday. But in the middle of the cake was written &#8216;7&#8217;. And by seeing this number, the curiosity of the fans has disappeared. A few days ago, the European media reported that Garnacho will get Cristiano Ronaldo&#8217;s iconic number 7 jersey next season after gaining the trust of United coach Eric Ten Haag . After seeing the number &#8216;7&#8217; on the birthday cake, fans made two-two-four.</p>



<p>In 2021, Ronaldo returned to United after an era in a dramatic change of team. Edinson Cavani willingly took the number 21 jersey and gave Ronaldo back his well-known &#8216;number seven&#8217;. But CRSeven&#8217;s second chapter at the English Premier League&#8217;s most successful club has not been pleasant. The Portuguese forward became a member of the team after Eric ten Haag became the coach of the Red Devils. In an interview with journalist Piers Morgan before the World Cup in Qatar last year, he made explosive comments about the club and the coach. After that, United canceled the contract with Ronaldo .</p>



<p>The number 7 jersey has not been handed to anyone since Ronaldo left Old Trafford midway through the 2022–23 season. Because, according to Premier League rules, no player can change jersey number during the season. Now that the season is over, there&#8217;s no stopping him from wearing the iconic jersey number.</p>



<p>Garnacho, who has been wearing the number 49 jersey for United for so long, is getting his ideal Ronaldo jersey next season. The young winger posted a picture wearing the number 7 on his Instagram story. Now it&#8217;s time to match yourself like Ronaldo.</p>



<p>Garnacho scored 5 goals and 4 assists in 34 games for United in all competitions last season. These statistics may seem, what else! But in 19 of these 34 matches, he was brought down as a substitute. The opportunity to play full 90 minutes was given in only 2 matches. He was out of the field for 7 matches due to an injury in the middle. The way Garnacho is making the most of this limited opportunity was enough for Ronaldo to get the number 7 jersey. As United&#8217;s new &#8216;number seven&#8217;, Garnacho will surely get more time on the field next season.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://r4s31.cam.britannica.com/a-messi-ronaldo-on-garnachos-birthday/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
